[instrumental music]
[indistinct chattering on radio]
[Lisbon]
'Nice place!'
Where does a baseball scout
get this kind of money?
Barney Sloop?
He's got 15 players
in the majors right now
and a piece of
everything they make.
A million-dollar
eye for talent.
He spots 'em young
all over the world
brings 'em here,
trains 'em.
Gets 'em fat pro contracts.
Hmm. So you played.
I played a little.
Pitcher?
Controlling the action?
A man with the ball?
Ah, I stopped.
Which you still have
unresolved bad feelings about.
Yeah...now I see it.
That's why you joined the gang.
'Parents thought you
were wasting your time'
so they made you quit
baseball, crushed your dream.
You were angry about it, but you
couldn't express that directly
so you joined a gang as
an outlet for all that anger.
Actually, I tore my ACL.
- Nice try.
- Uh.
Meh. Parents.
It's funny, isn't it?
Big regrets in life
people keep to themselves.
I don't know.
I tell people about you.
- Nice one. A zinger.
- Mm.
High and tight.
[male #1]
'As close as we can tell'
'the murder occurred
around 10:30 p.m.'
- Thanks.
- Mm-hmm.
Eh. No big mysteries,
weapon-wise.
Looks like three or four blows.
Rage killing.
[Cho]
'The coroner estimates TOD'
'around 10:30 last night.'
[male #2]
'You're here, finally.'
Freddy Fitch, Barney's partner.
I wanna know who
did this, quickly.
Agent Lisbon.
This is Agent Cho. Jane.
Anything you need, it's yours.
- I can't believe it.
- This was his garden?
His peace garden, he called it.
A year or so ago he got
into all this Zenmalarkey.
Who had access to this area?
Everyone at the academy,
six players in residence
family members, uh, staff.
- We'll need a list.
- 'Sure, sure.'
But trust me, n-no one
here w-w-would hurt Barney.
You discovered the body?
[Freddy]
'I was out of town yesterday.'
'A high school clinic
in Portland.'
'Flew back early this morning.'
Came straight here,
found him like this. My God!
[male #3]
'Run, run, run! Come on!
Work it, Scotty, work it!'
[Lisbon]
'His body's still warm,
and they're training?'
I said they could skip
the workout. They wouldn't.
"Hold on to the dream."
That's what he told them.
Barney was like
a father to these kids.
- Pitching is legs!
- It's good, it's good..
Look, dad, I'm ahead of you!
Seems they have
their own fathers.
Ah, these kids are minors.
We bring the dads out to sign
off on deals, moral support.
'Scotty Sinclair
and Snake Gallidos.'
Five drooling
scouts coming today.
Maybe now isn't
the best time.
Barney set this up,
his last showcase.
I'm gonna honor that.
'It's what Barney would want.'
I know you gotta talk to them.
It's your job, but please..
Hey, we can let the kids
finish their practice.
Let's take a look at his house.
How do you know where it's at?
'Cause this thing is
a map of his whole life.
Work, garden, home.
Zenmalarkey.
[indistinct chattering]
I don't expect it's much to look
at, a simple bed or a thing or..
Oh!
[theme music]
Jane? Jane?
Hey, you alright?
- 'Jane?'
- I see it.
- 'Cigarette case.'
- 'A cigarette case. Yes!'
Yes! Very good.
But..
'...what's it made of, son?'
What kind of
cigarette case, Patrick?
'What would you say?'
What's it made of?
[chuckles]
Sterling silver.
[laughing]
Your sterling silver
cigarette case back, ma'am.
- Next object would be--
- The cigarette case.
It once belonged to someone
very, very close to you.
That's right.
Yes. The boy wonder sees all.
'The next object, Patrick.'
Someone who's passed on..
...quite recently.
Last month.
Your grandfather.
No.
Your grandmother.
She loves you.
Very much.
More than she
may have expressed.
What the hell was that?
Your grandmother
loves you very much?
Well, did you see her face?
- It was beautiful.
- No. It was a needless risk.
An heirloom she
carries with her.
That's a recent death.
And she's too young
for dead parents.
- So a grandparent.
- So what? I'd moved on.
It's a double act, kid.
You don't fly solo.
Now you're always saying,
"when you're working strong
work strong, be brave."
Well, I was working
strong, and I was right.
No...there is no right
if there's no payoff.
This is show business,
not show art.
Your stage clothes are
walking by themselves.
Wash 'em good.
[indistinct chattering]
Hey!
That private reading..
...it came through.
- You got it? When?
- Tomorrow.
This is a big score, Patty.
Big enough for us to
blow off this outfit
step up in class
and get ourselves
some new wheels even.
Only one thing worries me.
It's you, myboy.
You up to it?
Oh, you know I am.
Of course, you are.
The boy wonder sees all.
Can you stand up?
- Can you talk?
- Ouch.
I was talking.
- He needs to see a doctor.
- Yeah.
Wow. I've never caught
a foul ball before.
Technically, you still haven't.
- Cho, you take him.
- Yeah.
Oh, no, no, no. I'm fine.
- How many fingers?
- Six.
Haven't we got
a murder to solve?
- You were unconscious.
- No, I wasn't.
- Jane, you were.
- I was not.
Your turn.
Okay, I'll see a doctor.
- Uh, excuse me, doctor?
- Hmm?
I know. Real-life patient.
I'm excited too.
Barney lived simple.
All work, all the time, 24/7.
Left his wife,
gave her the big house.
A clean, simple life
that's all he wanted.
- Barney was married?
- 'Still is.'
[Freddy]
'Leslie, a piece of work.'
'Like I said, he
moved out a year ago.'
After their son died.
He was three.
Choked on a balloon.
'Leslie just fell apart.'
'Angry at Barney, the whole
world, couldn't get past it.'
I called her this morning
after I called you.
She wouldn't even
pick up the phone.
The way I see it...bad things
happen, and you deal with 'em.
And Barney did?
Uh, he put his head
down, went to work.
Found Snake in the Dominican and
Scotty somewhere in-in Kansas.
Meanwhile, Leslie is...stuck
living in a, in a world of hurt.
Hmm. I feel it.
Let's check
the wife, Leslie Sloop.
[keyboard keys clacking]
- Working.
- Okay.
Drinking like a fish..
...picking up strangers..
...callin' Barney at all hours..
...screamin'.
I don't get that
kind of anger.
Okay, her kid died.
Is-is that gonna bring him back?
You don't have kids.
No, I don't.
'Uh, the ballplayers
should be heading in.'
With Barney dead,
I'm assuming
that you get the, uh
controlling interest
in the academy.
- What's that got to do with it?
- Money.
Traditionally a very
popular motive.
Excuse me?
I imagine these two
had their differences
'the gold watch,
the Italian suit.'
Oh, I'm sorry,
the Taiwanese suit
made to look Italian.
I don't have to listen to this.
Not exactly emblems of
the clean, simple life.
There was a culture clash, yeah?
- No.
- Jane.
Plus, what is it exactly
you bring to the table?
Barney was the brains,
the real scout, the star.
I mean, the Sloop Academy.
Jealousy, motive number two.
I killed him.
I-I murdered my best friend.
- Did you?
- Jane, come on.
Get this jerk away from me.
Seriously, get it
off your chest.
- You'll feel a lot better.
- He was my friend!
How did that feel, crushing your
friend's skull with that bat?
- How did that feel?
- Hey, hey, hey.
- Back off now.
- I'm just checking him out.
And?
Well, ambivalent
reading, to be honest.
'Maybe he did it.
Maybe he didn't.'
But one thing he does
understand, that's anger.
No offense.
[Freddy]
None taken, jerk.
[sighs]
You think I can
skip these interviews?
- Please.
- Thanks.
[Lisbon]
'Scotty Sinclair?'
Doc Sinclair. He's 17.
You're talkin' to him,
you're talkin' to me.
[instrumental music]
[Snake]
'Two, maybe three months ago..'
...I was having control
trouble, my slider.
Mr. Sloop said I
needed to quiet my brain.
We raked together in his garden.
It worked.
I would never hurt Mr. Sloop.
He gave me everything.
He brought me here.
He hooked me up with great
coaches, regular school.
And money to live on?
An advance, some kind
of endorsement deal?
Got, like, ten free pairs.
Which we're gonna have to pay
back if he blows this showcase.
Barney cared. Okay?
He taught us how to
handle money, invest it.
He taught us how to handle life.
Are we done yet?
He's supposed to be
throwing right now.
Right, yeah.
Got it. Thanks, Frank.
Whew!
Barney's life insurance payout,
twenty million dollars.
Let me guess, sole
beneficiary Leslie Sloop.
Twenty million.
That's a pretty good motive.
For twenty million dollars
I'd kill you.
- Oh, really?
- No, I mean, I'm kidding.
- It was a joke.
- Huh.
- Still the machine.
- Let's go see her.
Someone needs parking lessons.
Who are you?
We're looking for Leslie Sloop.
Bitch ain't here, man,
and I called the real cops.
- Hey, man, what took you?
- Hey, Narcisco!
- Wait. You know him?
- You don't?
Narcisco Rubrero.
Walk-off homer,
game one, world series?
Huh. Well.
Help us out, Narcisco.
Where is she?
Let's go downtown
and get a statement.
- 'Alright.'
- Hold on, you guys.
- We got dibs here.
- She scratched my face.
I think I'm bleedin'.
Look, she smashes her car,
so she steals mine.
- My Lamborghini.
- Where did she go?
I got a gun in that car.
It's all legal.
I got, like a,
got like a permit.
- Narcisco, where is she?
- I don't know, man.
She kept screaming
about her little angel.
You know, she had to
see her little angel.
The son, Michael.
Hey. Hey! She stole my car!
So take it up
with the real cops.
Jane, Lisbon wants
us back at the office.
Jane, wrong way.
Jane!
[instrumental music]
What are you doing?
[rustling]
[music continues]
They say there's no
seasons in California
but that looks like fall.
No, looks like
you need a doctor.
I am kind of dizzy.
[clapping]
[male #4]
'One more time.'
[clanging]
[male #5]
'Okay, hotshot.'
'Female, third in line.'
[Jane]
'Okay.'
New mom, recently married.
One of her first days out.
He is gonna get
her a better ring.
- Who is?
- Members only.
[indistinct chattering]
[Jane]
'They hadto get married.'
[laughs]
Yeah, that's my boy.
You have x-ray eyes.
No doubt about it.
Whew!
- Jane?
- Hey.
I'm okay.
Whew!
Snake and Scotty are about
to pitch. We can't miss that.
Oh, Michael, I'm so sorry.
What did I do?
[sobbing]
Mrs. Sloop?
I'm with my son.
Mrs. Sloop, I'm sorry,
we need to talk to you
about your husband.
No, no. You need to go.
Really, you do.
Don't you see this is private?
[dramatic music]
I don't want to talk.
I just...I just,
I want to end this.
- Please, just leave me alone.
- I'm sorry. We can't do that.
You have to. Please.
Because I...I don't
know what else to do.
Mrs. Sloop.
Oh, my God. I'm so sorry.
I've never had children.
I-I can't even begin
to imagine your loss.
No. No, you can't.
So just stop.
Please, just leave me alone.
'Just stop talking.'
I'm not going to stop. I can't.
My sister, she
was just like you.
I don't, I don't
want to hear this.
She wanted it to
beover...for her.
It was always about her.
'She couldn't talk to me.'
- About what?
- About anything.
I'm her sister.
But she didn't.
Not to me, not to anybody.
She just ended it for her.
I don't know what else to do.
Give me the gun.
Put it down.
You don't wanna
do this. Not here.
Give me the gun.
[sobbing]
I'm so sorry, Michael.
[Rigsby]
'It's okay.
Come on. It's okay.'
[indistinct chattering]
Not now. You know that.
'Okay. Okay.'
Look, I'm busy here.
Your brother's tryout is today.
'No. No way.'
Bye.
[indistinct chattering]
- Hey.
- That's my older boy.
He's a pitcher,
just like Snake.
He's just as good too.
But he's 22.
In baseball years,
he's an old man.
Yeah, these pro teams, they
like 'em young these days.
Like Snake.
Plenty of time for improvement.
[indistinct chattering]
We caught a break.
The wife looks good for it.
What was that? Was that a fork?
- Did he just throw a forkball?
- It was a slider.
We gotta go. Lisbon wants you
to take a look at the wife.
"Slider?" You know,
I'm still a little dizzy.
You go. Really,
I-I, I'll get a ride.
People love
driving with me.
Couldn't find sunflowers.
'Not quite the same.'
[Lisbon]
'Leslie, where
were you last night?'
[Leslie]
'We went to the movies.'
I don't...I don't
remember which one.
You're not supposed to take
these when you're drinking.
It was so loud.
There were guns
and helicopters
and people screaming.
Ugh, there was
so much screaming.
Darn. These are
supposed to keep me calm.
[chuckles]
Just one a day.
That's what the doctor said.
That'll do the trick.
Leslie, did you go
and see Barney last night?
To see Barney?
Mr. Zen?Mr. Acceptance?
[scoffs]
Why would I do that?
- 'Tell us about Narcisco.'
- Narcisco?
Oh, yeah.
[chuckles]
He's one of Barney's players.
'I sometimes slept
with those guys.'
'Did you know that?'
I did that sometimes...
to make him mad.
He didn't even care.
She's going around and around.
But I think she's
gonna give it up.
I thought you were, uh,
amazing out there today.
I just, just wanted
to tell you that.
Thank you, I guess.
- Can I ask you something?
- I don't have a sister.
No.
I didn't remember one.
It just...came out.
[indistinct chattering]
Come on.
Come on. Come on!
Ah! What was that?
Come on, Scotty!
What are you thinkin'?
- 'Come on!'
- He gets down on him too much.
- The boy can throw.
- Mmm. He can hit too.
Last night in the cage,
he dinged me three times
'off my slider.'
Nobody touches my slider.
That man is gonna
kill the golden goose.
Scotty plays like this now.
Imagine when he's
18 or 20 years old.
He's only gonna get better.
'It's amazing, huh?'
[alarm blaring]
[indistinct chattering]
[carnival music]
Ah! There.
Hmm.
'I spent three long days
at that crummy hospital'
finding the mark...
setting up the play.
And now..
...it's time to get paid.
[intense music]
[whirring]
[instrumental music]
[whirring continues]
[whirring stops]
Hey! We've been waiting for you.
- How you doing?
- Whoo! Go, Cho!
Hey! CBI! Stop!
Hey! Get back here! Hey!
[whirring continues]
[instrumental music]
[Lisbon]
'Leslie, we talked to
five bars near the beach.'
Nothing.
After the movies, I had
an argument with Narcisco
and went to Barney's.
[crying]
He was sleeping...
in his garden.
- He wouldn't even talk to me.
- Leslie.
I'm his wife.
I'm the mother of his child.
Shouldn't he talk to me?
She was there that night,
but he was already dead?
If they were at
a 10 o'clock movie, it adds up.
She knew he was dead.
That's what pushed
her over the edge.
I didn't, I didn't kill him.
I couldn't, even if I wanted to.
What would I tell Michael?
Mmm, you should let her go.
Where? Even if she didn't
kill him, she needs help.
Your pants are ripped.
We found a witness
with immigration problems.
A baseball player, he was
very angry with Mr. Sloop.
- Yesterday afternoon?
- He was yelling. Loud.
He say Mr. Sloop
was stealing.
And Mr. Sloop,
he was very quiet.
He was trying to walk away,
but the baseball player
he followed him, very angry.
That's it?
Um, Mr. Sloop, he
went into his trailer.
Then he come out
and he show him some papers.
And then the baseball
player, he got quiet.
And that's when I left.
But he'd recognize
the player if he saw him again.
- Yes.
- Mmm.
[male #6]
'Alright, line up
facing the mirror.'
It's the biggest day of their
lives. Don't you get that?
Barney Sloop had his head
bashed in, Mr. Gallidos.
Big day for him too.
[instrumental music]
[music continues]
- Him.
- You sure?
Him at the end.
[male #3]
'It's just not true.'
- Dad--
- Hey! I've got this!
My boy doesn't lie.
- If he said he didn't--
- I did.
I went to see him, alright?
But, I mean, I didn't kill him.
- What were you arguing about?
- I don't believe it.
- You lied to me?
- Mr. Sinclair, please.
Yeah. I'm sorry
to disappoint you, dad.
What were you arguing about?
What did Barney steal?
He's not saying one word
because we're leaving now.
Mr. Fitch--
Scotty had an argument
with Barney hours before
the murder.
You got nothing to hold him on.
Not yet.
[instrumental music]
[Lisbon]
'He had an argument with
Barney. He was angry.'
He lied about it.
Who's to say Scotty
didn't go back that night
and kill the guy?
The kid didn't do it.
He was angry with his
dad, not with Sloop.
If you think he did it,
then check the cameras.
What camera?
The baseball field cameras.
Snake let slip
that he and Scotty
were out there last night.
Apparently, Scotty handled
Snake's slider very well.
- You sure you're alright?
- Yeah. I'm fine.
Security cam.
Should be time-stamped.
[Grace]
'The guy who manages
the multiplex in Castine City'
he remembers a drunk
couple fighting in the lobby.
The woman was screaming
about the movie being too loud.
Ten o'clock show.
Sound familiar?
Go and show him a picture
of Leslie and Narcisco.
If he IDs them,
that lets them out too.
We're clearing people. We're
supposed to be catching them.
Mmm.
[thud]
[female #1]
'We've tried everything.'
She finished her fourth
course of chemo last week.
And then the, uh, t-tumors
in her lungs are growing.
Cool shirt.
[chuckles]
Thank you.
[coughing]
[hissing]
[female #1]
'Now the doctors say
there's nothing they can do.'
'Just...make her comfortable.'
I know it...must be difficult.
So when I heard
about the crystal..
Ah, yes. The crystal.
[instrumental music]
Does it really work?
Will it shrink the tumors?
Observe.
Decide for yourself.
[music continues]
- Patrick?
- Ahem.
[music continues]
Son?
I'm sorry.
Patrick.
What's wrong?
Oh, he...it's
a stressful process.
He just needs some air.
Won't be long.
[coughing]
[indistinct chattering]
- Get up and get back in there.
- I can't do it. I can't.
Get up now. What part?
Hmm? What part can't you do?
The gag? That's easy.
I did the hard part.
I put the money in the tent.
All you gotta do is pick it up.
She's dying. Okay?
We're stealing
from a dying girl.
Okay. Yeah, we're all dying,
kid. Okay? We're all dying.
But what we're giving her
because, yeah, she'll
be dead by Tuesday
and needs it more
than most ishope.
Hmm? Do you get that?
I can't do it.
Okay.
You're either with
the show, or you're not.
You're a loser
or you're someone
who plays the losers.
And you can't just back
outwhen you feel like it
when it's morally convenient,
when you don't have the guts.
I've never backed out.
I've been carrying
you for a long time.
And it's not gettin'
any easier, son.
No one likes
an aging boy psychic.
Short pants don't look so good
on a kid that needs a shave.
Now.
You're gonna need
a new act. Mm.
'You're gonna work that
out all by yourself?'
'You going solo?'
[laughing]
Yes or no, boy?
Are you with it?
Are you with me?
Right now.
You gotta say. Come on.
[clears throat]
Seven twenty one.
That's the last time we see 'em.
Either one of them could
have gone back to Barney's.
Where you going?
Baseball academy
I was thinking.
Don't we have
to solve this thing?
Rigsby and Van Pelt are talking
to the theater manager now.
The wife? No, no. It wasn't her.
The murder weapon
was a baseball bat.
Baseball bat, baseball
academy, common sense.
- Do you know who the killer is?
- What do you think?
I think you said,
"what do you think?"
to make me think you do
so I'll go with you
'but really you don't.'
[chuckles]
Cho?
Baseball bat, baseball academy,
that's not common sense.
Great. We'll all go.
[instrumental music]
[Freddy]
'Alright, fellas, fellas'
'listen up here
a minute, please.'
Before we start..
...I just wanna say a few
words about Barney Sloop.
He was a great partner..
...a great friend to all of us
and most of all...a great friend
to the game of baseball itself.
- Yeah.
Let us bow our heads.
Okay then.
That brings us to Snake
Gallidos and Scotty Sinclair.
'Barney's last and maybe
his greatest discoveries.'
Two pitchers with
huge franchise potential.
In a few minutes, guys...
you're gonna see the future.
Meanwhile...grab
some food and a beer..
...and make sure you've
brought your checkbooks.
What are you doing here?
Well, we thought you
might be relieved to know
that we know you're
innocent, so...you can relax.
Go out there and be great.
- 'You're gonna be superstars.'
- That's right, baby.
Women, cars, adulation, buckets
of money all there for you.
So who cares if your dad steals
a little here and there, huh?
- Hey, he didn't steal.
- Really?
Yeah. He just set up
a new bank account.
Oh. Oh.
And that's what Barney told you
when you went
over there to argue
to, uh, accuse him of stealing.
That your dad opened a new
account without telling you.
I don't think you're
helping here, man.
Yes, you two...
you have the gift.
The question is this, what are
you gonna do with that gift?
- Play baseball?
- That's right.
You're gonna play baseball.
You're gonna sell
soap, you're gonna
be part of the big machine.
No, no, no. Not soap, man.
My own cologne.
"Snake. For men."
- That sounds good.
- So we sell ourselves.
I mean, what else
are we gonna do?
Well, I'm just saying be careful
that you sell your
talent and not your soul.
Don't let other people run
your lives, not even your dads.
And trust me, I know
what I'm talking about.
Oh, yeah?
[chuckles]
What's your talent, old man?
Me? Uh..
I read minds, and there's been
plenty of times
that I've misused that.
Read minds, man? Get real.
I am real.
Just like most
people read books
I...read minds.
[snaps fingers]
Okay, what am I thinking?
You're thinking,
"Holy crap, I hope he can't
really read minds. Otherwise I'd
be in deep trouble right now."
Right?
[Snake and Scotty laughing]
Okay. Cho, could you hand
me that pencil, please?
Scotty, concentrate.
Think of your birthday.
Don't tell me.
Month, day, year. Concentrate.
Alright. I'm doing it.
He's messing with us, man.
- 'Come on, we need to go--'
- Shh!
I'm reading his mind.
[instrumental music]
Okay, got it.
[music continues]
What's your birthday, Scotty?
- April 10th, '92.
- "April 10th, '92."
Now how much money you wanna
bet that I can't read minds?
'You're gonna be a big
shot baseball player'
'make a lot of money.'
How much of that money
are you willing to bet
that I can't read minds?
No way.
Snake, you want
in on the action?
Cho's not going near it.
He knows better.
Show it to me.
No way. Come on. Show it.
[music continues]
- Okay, that's sick.
- Maybe he read it somewhere.
Snake, it's my talent.
You want to try? Your birthday.
Just think of it. It's okay.
[chuckles]
I got to warm up, man. Let's go.
Alright. Maybe another time.
- 'Good luck.'
- Thanks.
- 'You too.'
What was that about?
Just confirming a hunch.
[sighs]
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Just give me a minute,
I'll close this thing.
- My dad hated baseball.
- You gotta get over that.
Probably never would have
made the big leagues anyway.
This crystal
is from ancient Egypt.
'Its healing powers
are legendary.'
'Where there is sickness...
it brings health.'
This may be hard to watch.
No. Don't.
[coughing]
And when the crystal
is applied..
'...the burn is healed.'
[instrumental music]
The same thing
happens with the tumors.
- They just disappear.
- I want it.
Ma'am, we are here
for the next three days.
You can have as many
appointments as you like.
No!
I want the crystal.
I want to buy it.
Oh, that's not possible, ma'am.
- I brought cash.
- Ma'am, I'm sorry.
It's been in our family
for the past six generations.
- 'I can't.'
- Please.
I'm truly sorry, ma'am.
Dad...she needs it.
Just give it to her!
Please!
I'm begging you.
[laughing]
Ten grand, my son.
You were great in there.
The crying, oh,
that was fantastic.
I almost bought it myself.
You earned this. Every penny.
I'm gonna be
a little late tonight.
'The sideshow boys got
a little poker going.'
So, uh...wish me luck, hmm?
[instrumental music]
[bell ringing]
Snake, you left before
I got to read your mind.
What are you talking about?
Go away now. We got to focus.
Oh, I was just trying
to get his date of birth.
March 5th,'92. Okay? You happy?
March 5th,'92. That's weird.
I got the March 5th bit right,
but I got the, uh, year wrong.
Never off by that much.
Mmm, five years.
What are you doing?
That would make you
22, 22 years old.
Get out of here.
That's the same age as
your brother, uh, Carlos.
- That's his name, isn't it?
- Shut your mouth, man!
- Get outta here!
- Take it easy.
Barney found out,
didn't he? Yeah?
He found out that Snake was 22.
He was gonna send him home.
[whispering]
Shut your mouth, man.
What the hell's going on here?
Jupiter killed Barney
to conceal Snake's real age.
Holy crap. Is this true?
[Jupiter]
I tried to reason with him,
but he just walked away.
[thud]
- Papa?
- Don't say a word, Snake.
No digas nada.
He doesn't know nothing.
- Nothing about what?
- Holy crap.
I...I didn't do nothing.
I'm not saying nothing.
Oh, Jupiter, come on.
Let's be honest here.
We'll let your kid throw.
Right, Mr. Fitch? Yeah?
How old are you really,
kid? On the bible.
Twenty two.
Then you might have a shot.
Middle reliever maybe.
Double my cut, he can throw.
Deal.
Put your hands behind your back.
You're under arrest for
the murder of Barney Sloop.
- Dad.
- Man up, kid.
Remember to keep the ball low.
You get in trouble,
throw 'em the slider.
[Cho]
Come on.
[instrumental music]
I just feel a little bit dizzy.
I'm just gonna take a knee.
I'm good.
[male #3]
'Come on!'
[male #7]
'Strike three. You're out.'
- 'Nice pitch.'
- Yes! Ha ha.
- Oh, you got lucky on that one.
- I-I struck him out.
You set him up with the heater.
You don't use it for an out,
not in that situation.
I struck him out.
We'll talk about this later.
- I'm gonna make our deal.
- No. You won't.
I hired an agent.
[instrumental music]
Let's go see a doctor.
- Why? Are you feeling unwell?
- No, you are.
- Cho said you almost fainted.
- Oh, I was just pretending.
I hate these kind
of dramatic scenes. Poor kid.
Liar. You just don't
wanna go to the doctor.
Well, what's
a doctor gonna say?
"You banged your head.
Be careful."
- You might need an MRI.
- Oh.
Now you're really
selling it. Sounds great.
Are you okay?
Just kidding.
[instrumental music]
[male narrator]
Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
[theme music]